

Vădean Flaviu-Alexandru

🗣 Cluj-Napoca, Romania 📞 0757371684 💌 vadean.flaviu.alex@gmail.com

Introvert and charismatic student, with a passion for technology and art. Studying computer science came with challenges that have put me on a guest for knowledge and experience.

Work Experience

Web Developer 07/2022 - 08/2022

Transart

- I joined Transart's apprenticeship program to learn the fundamentals of full stack web development.

Building Caretaker 01/2020 - 04/2020

Medline

- Improved my endurance to repetitive tasks in an unchanging environment.

Chef 07/2019 - 09/2019

Taco Bell

- Developed additional team work skills while completing orders under a strict deadline.

Education

Faculty of Mathematics and Computer Science in English

2020 - present

Babes-Bolyai University

Technical (IT) Skills

Tools Database Management

Eclipse, MS Visual Studio, Scene Builder, SSMS MySQL

Languages

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Java, C#

Soft Skills

Communication, Teamwork, Flexibility, Problem Solving, Open-mindedness

Interests

Programming, Content creation, UI and UX design, Technology